<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Dong Liang's Blog</title><description>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.11</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 21:52:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Code Book - Test page 2</title><description>&lt;h1 id="codebook"&gt;Code Book&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id="datasource"&gt;Data Source&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code book is provided to  indicate all the variables and summaries calculated, along with units, and any other relevant information. The data used in this analysis was previously downloaded from the weblink as follows: &lt;a href="https://d396qusza40orc.cloudfront.net/getdata%2Fprojectfiles%2FUCI%20HAR%20Dataset.zip" title="Smart phone dataset"&gt;Data source&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="datacollection"&gt;Data Collection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A group of 30 volunteers at ages&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/19/code-book-test-page-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2e1e7253-bcd0-49e4-a697-cbef7d1c3112</guid><dc:creator>Dong Liang</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 21:52:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1 id="codebook"&gt;Code Book&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id="datasource"&gt;Data Source&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code book is provided to  indicate all the variables and summaries calculated, along with units, and any other relevant information. The data used in this analysis was previously downloaded from the weblink as follows: &lt;a href="https://d396qusza40orc.cloudfront.net/getdata%2Fprojectfiles%2FUCI%20HAR%20Dataset.zip" title="Smart phone dataset"&gt;Data source&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="datacollection"&gt;Data Collection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A group of 30 volunteers at ages ranging from 19 to 48 years old were enrolled in this video recorded experiment. Briefly, each individual was required to wear a Samsung Galaxy S II waist smartphone while performing six regular daily activities including WALKING, WALKING_UPSTAIRS, WALKING_DOWNSTAIRS, SITTING, STANDING and LAYING. At a constant rate of 50Hz, the 3-axial linear acceleration and 3-axial angular velocity were captured by Samsung smartphones using the embedded the accelerometer and gyroscope. The data were then manually labeled and according to the video recorded during the experiment. The final datasets were generated by randomly partitioning 70% of the volunteers into the training group and 30% of the rest into the test group. More info about the study can be retrieved from the &lt;a href="http://archive.ics.uci.edu/ml/datasets/Human+Activity+Recognition+Using+Smartphones" title="UCI machine learning repository"&gt;UCI machine learning repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="datasetinformation"&gt;Dataset Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The raw dataset includes the following files:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'README.txt'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'features_info.txt': Shows information about the variables used on the feature vector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'features.txt': List of all features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'activity_labels.txt': Links the class labels with their activity name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/X_train.txt': Training set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/y_train.txt': Training labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'test/X_test.txt': Test set.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'test/y_test.txt': Test labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following files are available for the train and test data. Their descriptions are equivalent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/subject_train.txt': Each row identifies the subject who performed the activity for each window sample. Its range is from 1 to 30. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/Inertial Signals/total&lt;em&gt;acc&lt;/em&gt;x&lt;em&gt;train.txt': The acceleration signal from the smartphone accelerometer X axis in standard gravity units 'g'. Every row shows a 128 element vector. The same description applies for the 'total&lt;/em&gt;acc&lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;train.txt' and 'total&lt;em&gt;acc&lt;/em&gt;z_train.txt' files for the Y and Z axis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/Inertial Signals/body&lt;em&gt;acc&lt;/em&gt;x_train.txt': The body acceleration signal obtained by subtracting the gravity from the total acceleration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'train/Inertial Signals/body&lt;em&gt;gyro&lt;/em&gt;x_train.txt': The angular velocity vector measured by the gyroscope for each window sample. The units are radians/second. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id="notes"&gt;Notes:  &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Features are normalized and bounded within [-1,1].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each feature vector is a row on the text file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about this dataset contact: activityrecognition@smartlab.ws&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="variablesandfeatureselection"&gt;Variables and Feature Selection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The features selected for this database come from the accelerometer and gyroscope 3-axial raw signals tAcc-XYZ and tGyro-XYZ. These time domain signals (prefix 't' to denote time) were captured at a constant rate of 50 Hz. Then they were filtered using a median filter and a 3rd order low pass Butterworth filter with a corner frequency of 20 Hz to remove noise. Similarly, the acceleration signal was then separated into body and gravity acceleration signals (tBodyAcc-XYZ and tGravityAcc-XYZ) using another low pass Butterworth filter with a corner frequency of 0.3 Hz. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subsequently, the body linear acceleration and angular velocity were derived in time to obtain Jerk signals (tBodyAccJerk-XYZ and tBodyGyroJerk-XYZ). Also the magnitude of these three-dimensional signals were calculated using the Euclidean norm (tBodyAccMag, tGravityAccMag, tBodyAccJerkMag, tBodyGyroMag, tBodyGyroJerkMag). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally a Fast Fourier Transform (FFT) was applied to some of these signals producing fBodyAcc-XYZ, fBodyAccJerk-XYZ, fBodyGyro-XYZ, fBodyAccJerkMag, fBodyGyroMag, fBodyGyroJerkMag. (Note the 'f' to indicate frequency domain signals). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These signals were used to estimate variables of the feature vector for each pattern: &lt;br&gt;
'-XYZ' is used to denote 3-axial signals in the X, Y and Z directions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAcc-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tGravityAcc-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAccJerk-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyro-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyroJerk-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAccMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tGravityAccMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAccJerkMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyroMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyroJerkMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyAcc-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyAccJerk-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyGyro-XYZ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyAccMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyAccJerkMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyGyroMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fBodyGyroJerkMag&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The set of variables that were estimated from these signals are: &lt;br&gt;
- mean(): Mean value
- std(): Standard deviation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional vectors obtained by averaging the signals in a signal window sample. These are used on the angle() variable:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gravityMean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAccMean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyAccJerkMean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyroMean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tBodyGyroJerkMean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other variables include subject and acitvity that denote the sample ID and the recorded acitvities respectively. Please find detailed data transformation info in the README document. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://ghost.org/images/ghost-mobile-642x.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>测试页面</title><description>&lt;p&gt;测试&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/19/ce-shi-ye-mian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">59689540-a951-4a15-a42e-99a726a045fc</guid><dc:creator>Dong Liang</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 20:11:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;测试&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Welcome to Ghost</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You're live! Nice. We've put together a little post to introduce you to the Ghost editor and get you started. You can manage your content by signing in to the admin area at &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;your blog URL&amp;gt;/ghost/&lt;/code&gt;. When you arrive, you can select this post from a list&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/03/19/welcome-to-ghost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b56f35c8-f198-47f0-b922-56cb6c689528</guid><category>Getting Started</category><dc:creator>Dong Liang</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 08:00:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You're live! Nice. We've put together a little post to introduce you to the Ghost editor and get you started. You can manage your content by signing in to the admin area at &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;your blog URL&amp;gt;/ghost/&lt;/code&gt;. When you arrive, you can select this post from a list on the left and see a preview of it on the right. Click the little pencil icon at the top of the preview to edit this post and read the next section!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="gettingstarted"&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ghost uses something called Markdown for writing. Essentially, it's a shorthand way to manage your post formatting as you write!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing in Markdown is really easy. In the left hand panel of Ghost, you simply write as you normally would. Where appropriate, you can use &lt;em&gt;shortcuts&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;style&lt;/strong&gt; your content. For example, a list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number two
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A nested item&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A final item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or with numbers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember to buy some milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drink the milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tweet that I remembered to buy the milk, and drank it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id="links"&gt;Links&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to link to a source? No problem. If you paste in a URL, like &lt;a href="http://ghost.org"&gt;http://ghost.org&lt;/a&gt; - it'll automatically be linked up. But if you want to customise your anchor text, you can do that too! Here's a link to &lt;a href="http://ghost.org"&gt;the Ghost website&lt;/a&gt;. Neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="whataboutimages"&gt;What about Images?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images work too! Already know the URL of the image you want to include in your article? Simply paste it in like this to make it show up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://ghost.org/images/ghost.png" alt="The Ghost Logo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure which image you want to use yet? That's ok too. Leave yourself a descriptive placeholder and keep writing. Come back later and drag and drop the image in to upload:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="quoting"&gt;Quoting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a link isn't enough, you want to quote someone on what they've said. Perhaps you've started using a new blogging platform and feel the sudden urge to share their slogan? A quote might be just the way to do it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ghost - Just a blogging platform&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id="workingwithcode"&gt;Working with Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got a streak of geek? We've got you covered there, too. You can write inline &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; blocks really easily with back ticks. Want to show off something more comprehensive? 4 spaces of indentation gets you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;.awesome-thing {
    display: block;
    width: 100%;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="readyforabreak"&gt;Ready for a Break?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw 3 or more dashes down on any new line and you've got yourself a fancy new divider. Aw yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h3 id="advancedusage"&gt;Advanced Usage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There's one fantastic secret about Markdown. If you want, you can write plain old HTML and it'll still work! Very flexible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="text" placeholder="I'm an input field!"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That should be enough to get you started. Have fun - and let us know what you think :)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>